<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Laundry Express</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="about_us">Welcome to Laundry Express, your one-stop solution for all your laundry needs. We understand that your time is precious, and laundry can take up a significant portion of it. That is why we have created an easy and convenient way to get your laundry done without hassle using our app.</string>

    <string name="text_two_lines">Primis odio inceptos condimentum viverra vehicula eros. Egestas pharetra sagittis vestibulum libero ligula mattis per.</string>

    <string name="step_1">Step 1: Schedule a Pick-up -
       Using our laundry express app, you can schedule a convenient date and time for us to pick up your laundry with our laundry shop partners. We will arrive at your specified location and collect your laundry.</string>

    <string name="step_2">Step 2: Select preferred services -
      Our laundry shop partners have some services that will suit your needs. You just need to Choose the services you preferred on your booking and our professional partners will handle it with their utmost care for you.</string>

    <string name="step_3">Step 3: Delivery -
       Once your laundry is ready, we will send you a notification through the app. You can then schedule a time for them to deliver your laundry back to you. Our delivery drivers will arrive at your specified location, and your clean laundry will be handed over to you.</string>

    <string-array name="sex">
        <item name="Select">Select sex</item>
        <item name="Male">Male</item>
        <item name="Female">Female</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>